listings.sg 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Listings.SG

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to implementing policies and procedures designed to protect your privacy and security. We want you to understand what kinds of information we gather about you, how this information is used and safeguarded, and how you can control its use.

In conjunction with this Privacy Policy, you should also review our Terms of Use for a complete understanding of the rules governing our Sites. This privacy policy covers the following issues:

  1. [Introduction](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap1 "Introduction")
  2. [Information we receive](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap2 "Information we receive")
  3. [Sharing information on LISTINGS.SG](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap3 "Sharing information on LISTINGS.SG")
  4. [How we use your information](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap4 "How we use your information")
  5. [How we share your information](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap5 "How we share your information")
  6. [How you can change or remove information](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap6 "How you can change or remove information")
  7. [How we protect your information](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap7 "How we protect your information")
  8. [Other terms](http://www.listings.sg/help/privacy#cap8 "Other terms")

### Introduction

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact our privacy administrator at   
Email protected.  
. This privacy policy covers the website www.listings.sg, it does not, apply to entities that LISTINGS.SG does not own or control. By using or accessing this website, you agree to our privacy practices outlined here.

### Information we receive

One of the primary reasons people use LISTINGS.SG is to share content with others. The information we receive from you will vary, depending on the activities you perform and the information you reveal to others.

When you make a comment or share content with others, an accompanying action will be shared as well. For example, if you were to upload photos, in addition to storing the actual photos you uploaded, the acitivty of the upload will be shared too.

We may collect information of you from activities whether directly or indirectly performed by people on LISTINGS.SG.

When you access LISTINGS.SG from a computer, mobile phone, or other devices, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit.

"Cookies" are small pieces of data we store for an extended period of time on your computer, mobile phone, or other devices you use to access the LISTINGS.SG. Cookies enable us to make LISTINGS.SG easier to use, tailor advertising to suit you better, and to protect both you and LISTINGS.SG. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, however, this will inhibit the performance and your experience of LISTINGS.SG.

We do not process payments from you directly. Whenever you initiate a payment to us, the process will be completed via an external third party payment processing provider. We do not store the details of your financial institution.

### Sharing information on LISTINGS.SG

This section explains how your privacy settings work, and how your information is shared. You should always consider your privacy settings before sharing information.

Designed to make it easy for you to find and connect with others, your name and profile photo do not have privacy settings. If you are uncomfortable with sharing your profile picture, you should delete it.

Your contact information privacy settings determines who can see your contact information such as your email and phone number(s). These additional information are non-mandatory and you do not have to share your email address with anyone.

Your personal information privacy settings determines who can see your personal information. We recommend that you share using the indirect connections setting.

The content you share and the activity you perform will show up on the home page. If another user tags you, you can remove the tag. Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others. You understand that information might be reshared or copied by other users.

Certain types of communications that you send to other people cannot be removed, such as messages. When you post information on another person's profile or comment on another person's post, that information will be subject to the other person's privacy settings.

Any piece of information set to “everyone” is publicly available information, just like your name, profile picture, and connections. Such information may, for example, be accessed by everyone on the Internet (including people not logged into LISTINGS.SG), be indexed by third party search engines, and be imported, exported, distributed, and redistributed by us and others without privacy limitations. Such information may also be associated with you, including your name and profile picture, even outside of LISTINGS.SG, such as on public search engines and when you visit other sites on the Internet. The default privacy setting for certain types of information you post on LISTINGS.SG is set to “everyone.” You can review and change the default settings in your privacy settings. If you delete “everyone” content that you posted on LISTINGS.SG, we will remove it from your profile, but have no control over its use outside of the site.

### How we use your information

We use the information collected to try to provide a safe, efficient, and personalised experience for you. Here are some of the details on how we do that:

We use the information to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features. We use the information to monitor and prevent potentially illegal activities as well as to detect and address issues such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users.

We do not share your information with advertisers. We do however, allow advertisers to choose the non-personally identifiable attributes of users who will see their advertisements. Even though we do not share your information with advertisers without your consent, when you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement there is a possibility that the advertiser may place a cookie in your browser and note that it meets the criteria they selected.

To help people find you. We allow other users to use contact information they have about you, such as your email address, to find you.

### How we share your information

When you ask us to invite a friend to join you on LISTINGS.SG, we will send your friend a message on your behalf using your name. The invitation may also contain information about other users your friend might know.

We may provide information to service providers that help us bring you the services we offer. For example, we may use external third parties to help host our website, send out email updates about LISTINGS.SG, remove duplicate information from our user lists, process payments, or provide search results or links. These service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service.

We may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters) if we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law. This may include respecting requests from jurisdictions outside of the Singapore where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with generally accepted international standards. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

### How you can change or remove information

You may change or remove your profile information at any time by going to your profile page and clicking “Edit My Profile.” Information will be updated immediately.

If you want to stop using your account you may deactivate it. We save your profile information (connections, photos, etc.) in case you later decide to reactivate your account. Many users deactivate their accounts for temporary reasons and in doing so are asking us to maintain their information until they return. You will still have the ability to reactivate your account and restore your profile in its entirety.

Even after you remove information from your profile or deactivate your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. However, your name will no longer be associated with that information.

Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies for up to 60 days, but will not be available to others.

If a person provides your email address to us, and you are not a LISTINGS.SG user but you want us to delete your address, you can do so on this help page. However, that request will only apply to addresses we have at the time of the request and not to any addresses that users provide to us later.

### How we protect your information

We also use automated and social measures to enhance security, such as analysing account behavior for fraudulent or otherwise anomalous behavior, may limit use of site features in response to possible signs of abuse, may remove inappropriate content or links to illegal content, and may suspend or disable accounts for violations of our Terms of Use.

Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorised persons will view your information. We cannot ensure that information you share will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up to date antivirus software.

You should report any security violations to us using the help page.

### Other terms

Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by publication here.

By using LISTINGS.SG, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the Singapore.

Defined Terms. "Us," "we," "our," and "LISTINGS.SG" mean the same as they do in the Terms of Use. “Information” and “content” are interchangeably used here unless otherwise limited by the context.

|
